[{"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 4], [2, 3], [4, 1], [3, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 5], [2, 3], [5, 1], [3, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 3], [2, 4], [3, 1], [4, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 3], [2, 5], [3, 1], [5, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 5], [2, 4], [5, 1], [4, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 4], [2, 5], [4, 1], [5, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 4], [3, 2], [4, 1], [2, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 5], [3, 2], [5, 1], [2, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 3], [4, 2], [3, 1], [2, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 3], [5, 2], [3, 1], [2, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 5], [4, 2], [5, 1], [2, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 4], [5, 2], [4, 1], [2, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 2], [3, 4], [2, 1], [4, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 2], [3, 5], [2, 1], [5, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 2], [4, 3], [2, 1], [3, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 2], [5, 3], [2, 1], [3, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 2], [4, 5], [2, 1], [5, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 2], [5, 4], [2, 1], [4, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 5], [3, 4], [5, 1], [4, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 4], [3, 5], [4, 1], [5, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 5], [4, 3], [5, 1], [3, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 4], [5, 3], [4, 1], [3, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 3], [4, 5], [3, 1], [5, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[1, 3], [5, 4], [3, 1], [4, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 4], [1, 3], [4, 2], [3, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 5], [1, 3], [5, 2], [3, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 3], [1, 4], [3, 2], [4, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 3], [1, 5], [3, 2], [5, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 5], [1, 4], [5, 2], [4, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 4], [1, 5], [4, 2], [5, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 4], [1, 2], [4, 3], [2, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 5], [1, 2], [5, 3], [2, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 3], [1, 2], [3, 4], [2, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 3], [1, 2], [3, 5], [2, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 5], [1, 2], [5, 4], [2, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 4], [1, 2], [4, 5], [2, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 2], [1, 4], [2, 3], [4, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 2], [1, 5], [2, 3], [5, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 2], [1, 3], [2, 4], [3, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 2], [1, 3], [2, 5], [3, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 2], [1, 5], [2, 4], [5, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 2], [1, 4], [2, 5], [4, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 5], [1, 4], [5, 3], [4, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 4], [1, 5], [4, 3], [5, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 5], [1, 3], [5, 4], [3, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 4], [1, 3], [4, 5], [3, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 3], [1, 5], [3, 4], [5, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 3], [1, 4], [3, 5], [4, 1]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 4], [3, 1], [4, 2], [1, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 5], [3, 1], [5, 2], [1, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 3], [4, 1], [3, 2], [1, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 3], [5, 1], [3, 2], [1, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 5], [4, 1], [5, 2], [1, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 4], [5, 1], [4, 2], [1, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 4], [2, 1], [4, 3], [1, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 5], [2, 1], [5, 3], [1, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 3], [2, 1], [3, 4], [1, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 3], [2, 1], [3, 5], [1, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 5], [2, 1], [5, 4], [1, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 4], [2, 1], [4, 5], [1, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 2], [4, 1], [2, 3], [1, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 2], [5, 1], [2, 3], [1, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 2], [3, 1], [2, 4], [1, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 2], [3, 1], [2, 5], [1, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 2], [5, 1], [2, 4], [1, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 2], [4, 1], [2, 5], [1, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 5], [4, 1], [5, 3], [1, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 4], [5, 1], [4, 3], [1, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 5], [3, 1], [5, 4], [1, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 4], [3, 1], [4, 5], [1, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 3], [5, 1], [3, 4], [1, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 3], [4, 1], [3, 5], [1, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 1], [3, 4], [1, 2], [4, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 1], [3, 5], [1, 2], [5, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 1], [4, 3], [1, 2], [3, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 1], [5, 3], [1, 2], [3, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 1], [4, 5], [1, 2], [5, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 1], [5, 4], [1, 2], [4, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 1], [2, 4], [1, 3], [4, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 1], [2, 5], [1, 3], [5, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 1], [2, 3], [1, 4], [3, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 1], [2, 3], [1, 5], [3, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 1], [2, 5], [1, 4], [5, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 1], [2, 4], [1, 5], [4, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 1], [4, 2], [1, 3], [2, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 1], [5, 2], [1, 3], [2, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 1], [3, 2], [1, 4], [2, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 1], [3, 2], [1, 5], [2, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 1], [5, 2], [1, 4], [2, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 1], [4, 2], [1, 5], [2, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 1], [4, 5], [1, 3], [5, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 1], [5, 4], [1, 3], [4, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 1], [3, 5], [1, 4], [5, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 1], [3, 4], [1, 5], [4, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 1], [5, 3], [1, 4], [3, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 1], [4, 3], [1, 5], [3, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 5], [3, 4], [5, 2], [4, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 4], [3, 5], [4, 2], [5, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 5], [4, 3], [5, 2], [3, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 4], [5, 3], [4, 2], [3, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 3], [4, 5], [3, 2], [5, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[2, 3], [5, 4], [3, 2], [4, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 5], [2, 4], [5, 3], [4, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 4], [2, 5], [4, 3], [5, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 5], [2, 3], [5, 4], [3, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 4], [2, 3], [4, 5], [3, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 3], [2, 5], [3, 4], [5, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 3], [2, 4], [3, 5], [4, 2]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 5], [4, 2], [5, 3], [2, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 4], [5, 2], [4, 3], [2, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 5], [3, 2], [5, 4], [2, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 4], [3, 2], [4, 5], [2, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 3], [5, 2], [3, 4], [2, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 3], [4, 2], [3, 5], [2, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 2], [4, 5], [2, 3], [5, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[3, 2], [5, 4], [2, 3], [4, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 2], [3, 5], [2, 4], [5, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 2], [3, 4], [2, 5], [4, 3]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[4, 2], [5, 3], [2, 4], [3, 5]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "count-things", "title": "填一填", "stem": "从左往右数", "stem2": "合起来有", "sum": 5, "unit": "朵", "name": "花", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [[5, 2], [4, 3], [2, 5], [3, 4]], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-04"}]